Hello friends welcome to Smart
Wealth Advisors today the long results are out and first of all let me give a
disclaimer in the match
not a great warrior and this stock is a great
value in my portfolio and I have been
invested in it for a very long time I
am a mister so you can do this in some
way home advices that even from camera footage
registered advisor ok Mulayam Singh on this
occasion on bride information so let's move that
distinguished disclaimer
because it happens that if you
write full like not true love you want to listen then there is a
difference between subscribe and like that
system channel and whatever may be the hatred towards it
okay someone can
take a long time can
come okay but mostly what happens is
online secure life
insurance where your premium is for a
very long time than this big dormant
2025 process like term insurance
and it happens okay so another
small figure net head will look small interview compare
with life insurance company  Okay,
but you can subscribe to smaller channels in the fog on the side.
Okay, so now
pick up from school, but its net profit is six,
and here I have one because
like I have 500ml and
fast, whatever money is collected, whatever
premium is collected, I take it out and
tell it in the customer diary, okay, so on
that entire, when it starts turning white, then
its texture is there, there is an option day,
Tulsi's return rate policy, Angry
Birds Solar behind, Group Budget Hitech,
just front subscribe. The Amazing 9
percent increase has happened, so such a general
appointment and a lot of money is like
in the gland, but at the same time,
thank you, share the link
from a big company, okay, so there,
like the light went on, we will do
RIMS, which is a big insurance company,
so I got four shrinks, four in the
morning, I have referred RIMS for three hundred crores, so the
swelling refund on my net,
they went to the road, 300 courts,
okay, like this, it gets a little difficult
with normal business, but such a tweet  You ca
n't understand that
when that text is added, the
TVS, from this point the one percent that is
visible, it looks a little more,
okay, it is
just a little difference, now let's
come to your amount received on this -
1898 company Dhundh Withdrawn in, I invested
₹100 from medium, so my 97.9 minutes went so much, that
means not a single penny on it
till writing, and the old balance of 06
Agra, so there their jewellery guest
Belur Math - you will read sesame construction 130
0, means do subscribe, now you should
subscribe to this, you can subscribe our channel and
subscribe. The amazing loss is this, it is very
subscribe, definitely subscribe, that means
in the equity of government securities, okay, so it
also went up so much
last year in this card, 10 minutes 80
crore up capital gain body 718 crore capital
gain tax like this is water general
insurance company will reduce it,
subscribe to this channel, then it becomes so big
that subscribe which is 16
so that  Remind me, if you keep doing it then
understand that there will definitely be profit,
not less than that, so like the shortcomings of this, like the
stress machine machine Rewa railway
track, that I will get
different results from oil, now with the help of screen, now
school, then subscribe to this, there is
health insurance, after that slowly
rain, definitely watch this video,
how much were you growing here, no, like show me
the half, okay, so you go and open the app,
read the report, chicken look into this
website and can read the complete report,
okay, thank you very much, thanks, if you liked the video then
like, share and subscribe to